<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>上がる</title>
    <link>https://www.agaru.be/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 上がる</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.agaru.be/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Devops &amp; VMSS - part2</title>
      <link>https://www.agaru.be/posts/azure-devops-vmss/part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.agaru.be/posts/azure-devops-vmss/part2/</guid>
      <description>Azure DevOps &amp;amp; VMSS agents Good news everyone! Azure DevOps now supports VMSS as agent.
In this series of posts, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover:
 Why use a VMSS with Azure DevOps? How to create and configure a simple VMSS. Customising the VMSS. Use Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s script to create an image for our VMSS. Getting freaky with those images. Some security aspects.  Azure CLI First, let&amp;rsquo;s install Azure CLI.
Create the VMSS We can now create the VMSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Devops &amp; VMSS - part1</title>
      <link>https://www.agaru.be/posts/azure-devops-vmss/part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.agaru.be/posts/azure-devops-vmss/part1/</guid>
      <description>Azure DevOps &amp;amp; VMSS agents Good news everyone! Azure DevOps now supports VMSS as agent.
In this series of posts, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover:
 Why use a VMSS with Azure DevOps? How to create and configure a simple VMSS. Customising the VMSS. Use Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s script to create an image for our VMSS. Getting freaky with those images. Some security aspects.  Why use VMSS with Azure DevOps? Private resources Unless you&amp;rsquo;re a startup or have committed to the cloud 200%, you&amp;rsquo;re likely to have private resources like IIS servers in an internal zone, an instance of SonarQube CE that you do not want to expose on the internet ever (why would you even do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting</title>
      <link>https://www.agaru.be/posts/hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.agaru.be/posts/hosting/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Here&amp;rsquo;s a first post about this webiste.
Intro Tools:
 Hugo Azure Statis Web Apps Github VScode Markdown  Hugo is an open-source static site generators based on Markdown. It allows you to generate static pages that requieres very few resources to serve. There will be some html, some css and some JS, and that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it. This will garantee an easy to maintain and very responsive website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.agaru.be/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.agaru.be/about/</guid>
      <description>Another tech blog.
上がる: to climb; to rise; to go up; to come up; to ascend; to advance
Who am I? Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Simon Michelizza, a 34 year old cloud architect. I&amp;rsquo;m mostly working with Azure, devops, Intune, AKS,&amp;hellip; And this is about sharing the good, and mostly the ugly so you don&amp;rsquo;t have too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
